== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Bernadette:)I'm worried about Howard.
Ever since that guy
(Bernadette:)from the Air Force showed up,
he's been a nervous wreck.
(Penny:)All right, we work at
a giant pharmaceutical company.
(Penny:)Get him some anti-anxiety meds.
(Bernadette:)He won't take any pills
that aren't chewable
(Bernadette:)and shaped like a Flintstone.
(Penny:)You know, when Leonard's
feeling anxious
(Penny:)I make him take a long walk.
(Amy:)Does that help?
(Penny:)Well, for a while.
Then he comes back.
(Bernadette:)I don't believe this.
(Amy:)What's wrong?
(Bernadette:)This guy from the office
just congratulated me
(Bernadette:)on being pregnant.
(Amy:)You did already know, right?
(Bernadette:)No one at the office did.
(Bernadette:)Did you tell
anyone?
(Raj:)No.
You told me not to.
(Bernadette:)I bet it was Barbara Chen
in retrovirus.
(Bernadette:)She might have heard me
throwing up one morning.
(Bernadette:)Every since she got
(Bernadette:)the hearing aid,
she thinks she's so great.
(Amy:)Why don't you want
anyone to know?
'Cause I'm up for a major
immunotherapy study,
(Bernadette:)and if they find out
I'm pregnant
(Bernadette:)they might give it
to someone else.
(Penny:)Would they really do that?